https://www.fanbridge.com/policies/privacy.php?ref=wordpress_plugin

Last Update: October 20, 2017
FanBridge.com is an email list management service provided by FanBridge, Inc.
To report any abuse or violations of the FanBridge service, please send email to
and attach an unedited copy of the email message that you feel was sent to you in error or without your permission. Include all header information so that we can trace origin of the message. Also include any notes or other information that you feel are pertinent. Any questions or concerns regarding this privacy policy may be directed to .
Children's Guidelines
This website is directed persons over the age of 13, and we do not seek to collect from children online contact information or distribution to third parties any personally identifiable information from children or entice children to divulge information to us. If the COPPA Compliance requirement setting is turned on for an account, then all submissions
from that time on will be required to submit a date of birth with a request to join the mailing list. Any subscription request comes with a date of birth of younger than 13 years of age, the submission will be denied right away. This filtering only applies for fan opt-ins and does not prohibit emails added by the account from being added.
Email and Direct Response Contact
All of our direct response methods are opt-in. If you subscribed to our email newsletter(s) but do not want to receive it in the future, please follow the "unsubscribe" instructions contained in the newsletter(s).
Website Information Collection
For each visitor to our web page, our web server automatically recognizes only the consumer's domain name or IP address, but not the email address. Unless otherwise stated on our website, we collect only the domain name or IP address of visitors to our web page, the email addresses of those who communicate with us via email, aggregate information on what pages consumers access or visit, user-specific information on what pages consumers access or visit, information volunteered by the consumer, such as survey information and registrations to access portions of the site and their related services or to set up a FanBridge account. We also collect clickstream information. We use SSL (secure socket layer) encryption for online payment collection for purchases of our own proprietary products and services, which includes the FanBridge email list management service.
Use of Website Information Collected
The information we collect is used to create an aggregate demographic profile of our user base so that we can improve the content and services of our website and provide aggregate information to potential advertisers (no individual information is provided to any third-party without your consent), to customize the content and/or layout of our page for each individual visitor, to notify consumers about updates to our Website and services, to send visitors our opt-in email newsletter(s) (if requested by the visitor), to provide users with the products and/or services for which they signed-up or registered which may include sending service disruption notices or other service- or product-related information via email, and is not shared with other organizations for commercial purposes without the visitor's consent. We may share collected information with another company in the event that we merge with or are acquired by another company. Customers may prevent their information from being used for purposes other than those for which it was originally collected by sending us email at the above address. Upon request we provide site visitors with access to contact information (e.g., name, address, phone number) that we maintain about them. You can access this information, and/or have it corrected, by logging into your account online.
Use of Your Email List Information
FanBridge is not an email list rental service and does not rent or sell any email addresses or other contact information that you provide or collect regarding your email list members. At all times, you retain ownership and control of your email lists and list information. When you schedule an email message to be broadcast to your list members, FanBridge sends your message based on the personalization, targeting, and other criteria that you specified when you created and scheduled your message. Please keep your account login and password secure at all times, changing your password regularly as you would on other computer systems to prevent unauthorized access or use. In order to comply with government legislation, email addresses which have requested no further contact will be placed on a suppression list which may be accessed by other organizations to maintain suppression of such addresses in their mailings as well as ours.
Cookies
We use cookies to record session information, such as items that consumers add to their shopping cart, record user-specific information on what pages users access or visit, record past activity at a site in order to provide better service when visitors return to our site, customize web page content based on visitors' browser type or other information that the visitor sends, and to enable access to specific areas on the website. We, or a data provider we have engaged, may place (via email or webpage) or recognize a unique cookie on your browser to enable you to receive customized ads, content or services. Our partners use this information to recognize you across different channels and over time for advertising, analytics, attribution, and reporting purposes. No personally identifiable information is placed into these cookies. The cookies may reflect data you voluntarily have submitted to us, e.g., your email address, and may be shared only in hashed, non-human readable form. To opt-out of these cookies, please go to http://www.aboutads.info/choices.
Security
We strive to maintain appropriate security measures in our physical facilities to protect against the loss, misuse or alteration of information that we have collected from you at our site. Although we take reasonable measures to secure our data, we cannot guarantee that the measures we take are or will remain adequate. Some portions of our sites and services link to other companies' websites. Please refer to the privacy policies of those sites for information on how they handle security for information they collect.
Postal Address Collection and Use
If you supply us with your postal address online, we will use it to send you the information for which you provided us your address. If you supply us with your telephone number online, we will use it to contact you with information regarding your account, orders your have placed, or with information regarding your inquiry. We may send you information about additional services that we offer, but we will not rent or sell your contact information to any third parties without your permission.
YouTube
FanBridge uses the YouTube API Services to fetch authorized YouTube content and analytics for seamless fan marketing and comprehensive data analysis. We comply with Google’s Privacy Policy, which can be read here: http://www.google.com/policies/privacy. Just like with email data, any YouTube data is your own and never shared with other FanBridge accounts. Any data stored from an authorization of your account will be deleted if the account (1) disconnects the authorization between YouTube and FanBridge from the Link Social page on FanBridge found here: https://www.fanbridge.com/socialnet/accounts/universal_connect.php, (2) revokes access remotely from Google’s security settings page found here: https://security.google.com/settings/security/permissions, or (3) fails to reauthorize the connection should the token expire. For any questions or complaints about the privacy practices of FanBridge’s connection to YouTube’s API Services, you may contact us at
Changes to Privacy Policy
From time to time, we may use customer information for new, unanticipated uses not previously disclosed in this Privacy Policy notice. If our information practices change at some time in the future, we will post the policy changes to our website's Privacy Policy page to notify you of these changes and provide you with the ability to opt out of these new uses. If you are concerned about how your information is used, you should check back at our website's Privacy Policy page periodically.
